(Bernadette:)Don't let that sway you.
(Howard:)It's hard not to. They taste so
much better than real berries.
(Stuart:)What's up?
(Bernadette:)So... we need to talk.
(Emily:)You okay?
(Raj:)I think we should talk.
(Stuart:)Is everything okay?
(Bernadette:)Well... you've been
living here a while now.
(Sheldon:)I know.
I may sell comic books at work,
(Stuart:)but the real superheroes
(Stuart:)are sitting
right in front of me.
(Penny:)Yeah...
(Howard:)His middle name is David. Go.
(Raj:)Look, I care about you a lot,
(Raj:)but we are very
different people.
(Emily:)Are you breaking up with me?
(Raj:)No, no, I'm just
pointing out that
(Raj:)you're dark on the inside
and I'm dark on the outside.
(Bernadette:)So, anyway,
what I'm trying to say is...